makingstarwars.net 2019-04-01

# Privacy and Disclaimer – Making Star Wars

## Privacy Policy:

MakingStarWars.net, LLC (“ **MakingStarWars.net** “) operates makingstarwars.net and may operate other websites. It is MakingStarWars.net’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, MakingStarWars.net collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MakingStarWars.net’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MakingStarWars.net’s visitors use its website. From time to time, MakingStarWars.net may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

MakingStarWars.net also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on makingstarwars.net blogs/sites. MakingStarWars.net only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to MakingStarWars.net’s websites choose to interact with MakingStarWars.net in ways that require MakingStarWars.net to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that MakingStarWars.net gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [makingstarwars.net](https://makingstarwars.net/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with MakingStarWars.net are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, MakingStarWars.net collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with MakingStarWars.net. MakingStarWars.net does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

MakingStarWars.net may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. MakingStarWars.net may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, MakingStarWars.net does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

MakingStarWars.net discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on MakingStarWars.net’s behalf or to provide services available at MakingStarWars.net’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using MakingStarWars.net’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MakingStarWars.net will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, MakingStarWars.net discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when MakingStarWars.net believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MakingStarWars.net, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an MakingStarWars.net website and have supplied your email address, MakingStarWars.net may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with MakingStarWars.net and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. MakingStarWars.net takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the Site for the purpose of creating better recommendations. We will use the session cookies to keep track of you whilst you navigate the Site. We will use the persistent cookies to enable the Site to recognise you when you visit.

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies may remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date. We use these persistent cookies to better serve you with the kinds of content that we feel may be of interest to you.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of the Site. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about the Site use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to the Site is used to create reports about the use of the Site. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

### Business Transfers

If MakingStarWars.net, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that MakingStarWars.net goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of MakingStarWars.net may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MakingStarWars.net and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, MakingStarWars.net may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MakingStarWars.net’s sole discretion. MakingStarWars.net encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a makingstarwars.net account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
